{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Xiānshēng",
      "answer": "先生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yào",
      "answer": "要"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shīfù",
      "answer": "师傅"
    },
    {
      "question": "Píngguǒ",
      "answer": "苹果"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duìbùqǐ",
      "answer": "对不起"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zěnme",
      "answer": "怎么"
    },
    {
      "question": "Róngyì",
      "answer": "容易"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pútáo",
      "answer": "葡萄"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jīn",
      "answer": "斤"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qián",
      "answer": "钱"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kuài",
      "answer": "块"
    },
    {
      "question": "Máo",
      "answer": "毛"
    },
    {
      "question": "Guì",
      "answer": "贵"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zuò",
      "answer": "做"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fēn",
      "answer": "分"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sòng",
      "answer": "送"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gěi",
      "answer": "给"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhǎo",
      "answer": "找"
    }


  ]
}
